const questions = [
    {
        // Question 1
        question: "Walter has permission to install a skylight in the roof of his townhouse. However, he is concerned about water leaking into his home. What should be used to prevent water from entering through the skylight?",
        choices: ["Zinc strips",
        "Metal flashing",
        "Aluminum polyethylene sheets",
        "Vinyl barge trim"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 2
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a typical characteristic of a green building?",
        choices: ["ENERGY STAR® windows filled with argon gas",
        "Built using an integrated design process",
        "A heating system using solar or geothermal energy",
        "Higher operating costs than a similar sized non-green building"],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        // Question 3
        question: "Tessa, a developer, is looking for a construction material that requires the least amount of additional fireproofing. Which of the following would her contractor MOST likely recommend?",
        choices: ["Steel frame",
        "Reinforced concrete",
        "Wood stud frame",
        "Masonry"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 4
        question: "Which of the following problems with a townhouse could NOT be discovered by a visual inspection of the townhouse’s exterior?",
        choices: ["Uneven settlement of the building",
        "Early stages of dry rot in structural members",
        "Edge curl of asphalt shingles",
        "None of these problems could be discovered by a visual inspection"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 5
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a top-level objective of the National Building Code or BC Building Code?",
        choices: ["safety",
        "Public health",
        "Aesthetics",
        "Fire protection"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        // Question 6
        question: "Which of the following statements regarding building envelope systems is TRUE?",
        choices: ["When a window is cracked, allowing a large amount of heat to escape from the home to the outside, it is known as a thermal broken window.",
        "Window drafts can be alleviated by sealing the joint between the window and the wall with caulking.",
        "Polystyrene insulation is sprayed into wall cavities and attics through small drilled holes.",
        "Cellulose fibre is made from shredded glassfibre batts, with chemicals added to prevent fungi."],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 7
        question: "The Enigma is a new apartment building. The distance from the bottom landing to the top floor of the Enigma is 275 feet. What is the minimum speed the elevator should be?",
        choices: ["550 fpm",
        "500 fpm",
        "275 fpm",
        "137.5 fpm"],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        // Question 8
        question: "You are inspecting a townhouse when you notice a fine, powdery sawdust throughout the home. Which of the following types of invisible defects is this MOST likely to be?",
        choices: ["An invisible defect of improper materials",
        "An invisible defect due to design",
        "An invisible defect due to improper maintenance",
        "An invisible defect due to a non-continuous vapour barrier"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        // Question 9
        question: "Which of the following statements regarding house finishes is FALSE?",
        choices: ["Sidewalks can be subject to settlement problems and replacement should be considered for safety reasons.",
        "Slight cracking in stucco siding is fairly common and does not necessarily indicate structural damage.",
        "Carpet flooring is generally installed directly on top of the rough plywood nailed to the floor joists.",
        "The main concern with deck rails is that they must be able to support lateral pressure from people’s weight."],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        // Question 10
        question: "Which of the following is NOT an example of functional obsolescence in multi-family residential properties?",
        choices: ["An interior finish that requires extensive maintenance",
        "A building design that fails to meet environmental certification standards",
        "A three-story building without elevators",
        "Units containing gas fireplaces and appliances"],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        // Question 11
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a use for insulation?",
        choices: ["Lessening the impact of sounds",
        "Keeping heat in during cooler months",
        "Keeping moisture out",
        "Keeping heat out during warmer months"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        // Question 12
        question: "Which of the following locations is LEAST likely to require a fire door?",
        choices: ["The entrance to a fire escape staircase",
        "The entrance to an individual suite",
        "The entrance to an electrical switch room",
        "The entrance from inside the building to a garage"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 13
        question: "Which of the following options BEST describes the primary purpose of flashing around a roof?",
        choices: ["To provide insulation between the roof and the interior of the house",
        "To make it easier to install the roof or to perform major repairs",
        "To provide an attractive, cohesive finish to the building exterior",
        "To direct rain-driven moisture away from the sealant around vertical penetrations of the roof"],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        // Question 14
        question: "Which of the following examples is MOST likely to be classified as a design defect?",
        choices: ["A strata unit where the main entrance opens directly into the master bedroom",
        "A bathroom where the wallpaper is peeling, despite being only one year old",
        "A sagging patio due to an inadequate foundation",
        "A lack of insulation between the interior and exterior walls"],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        // Question 15
        question: "Which of the following is NOT required in each unit of a multi-family building by the National Plumbing Code?",
        choices: ["A kitchen sink",
        "A shower or bath tub",
        "A source of domestic hot water, either in the suite or shared",
        "Laundry facilities"],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        // Question 16
        question: "Which of the following is likely to be the GREATEST concern with respect to a parking lot?",
        choices: ["The parking lot consists primarily of asphalt",
        "The parking lot slopes towards the building",
        "The parking spots are covered by a carport",
        "Each parking spot is associated with a specific unit"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 17
        question: "Which of the following is NOT an advantage of steel frame construction?",
        choices: ["It is non-combustible",
        "It is less expensive than reinforced concrete",
        "It does not have any shrinkage problems",
        "Fire resistance can be provided by drywall for walls and floors"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 18
        question: "Which of the following options is an example of curable functional obsolescence?",
        choices: ["A slow elevator",
        "Outdated kitchen counters",
        "Insufficient parking",
        "Poor HVAC systems"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 19
        question: "What is the term used for the portion of a building that extends above ground?",
        choices: ["Shear strength",
        "Superstructure",
        "Substructure",
        "Retaining structure"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 20
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a benefit of mechanical ventilation?",
        choices: ["Better indoor air quality",
        "Insulation from sound",
        "More control over the locations for fresh air intake",
        "Improved comfort due to the constant flow of fresh air"],
        correct: 1
    }
];